<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-07-14T21:02:11-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Joey Day</title><subtitle>Hi, I’m Joey. I’m a 30-something software engineer (read: big nerd) in Salt Lake City. When I grow up I’d like to be a seminary professor (read: even bigger nerd).
</subtitle><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><entry><title type="html">Merissa’s Wedding Day</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/30/merissas-wedding-day/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Merissa’s Wedding Day" /><published>2002-04-30T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-30T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/30/merissas-wedding-day</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/30/merissas-wedding-day/">&lt;figure class=&quot;alignleft&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/2002-04-30-merissa.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Beautiful Bride&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today is my sister’s wedding day. She is one of my best friends. I’ve seen her grow so much in the 20 years we’ve known each other. Never have I seen her more beautiful than today. Steve and Merissa: I want to congratulate both of you and extend my best wishes for a happy life together. I love you! &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">Today is my sister’s wedding day. She is one of my best friends. I’ve seen her grow so much in the 20 years we’ve known each other. Never have I seen her more beautiful than today. Steve and Merissa: I want to congratulate both of you and extend my best wishes for a happy life together. I love you! </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mom’s Birthday</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/29/moms-birthday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mom’s Birthday" /><published>2002-04-29T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-29T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/29/moms-birthday</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/29/moms-birthday/">&lt;p&gt;Happy Birthday, Mom! Thanks for always doing my laundry and cooking for me and lending me money and cleaning up after me and generally putting up with all of my crap. You are the best mother a guy could have. I love you! ❤️ &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">Happy Birthday, Mom! Thanks for always doing my laundry and cooking for me and lending me money and cleaning up after me and generally putting up with all of my crap. You are the best mother a guy could have. I love you! ❤️ </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">New Family Page</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/28/new-family-page/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="New Family Page" /><published>2002-04-28T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-28T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/28/new-family-page</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/28/new-family-page/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve finished my &lt;a href=&quot;/family&quot;&gt;Family&lt;/a&gt; page. I should’ve had this up a long time ago. I want to tell my family how much I love them. Mom, Dad, Merissa, you each mean so much to me and I can’t say enough how grateful I am for your love and support. Thank you for everything you’ve done for me. I love you! &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve finished my Family page. I should’ve had this up a long time ago. I want to tell my family how much I love them. Mom, Dad, Merissa, you each mean so much to me and I can’t say enough how grateful I am for your love and support. Thank you for everything you’ve done for me. I love you! </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Down to the Wire</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/27/down-to-the-wire/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Down to the Wire" /><published>2002-04-27T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-27T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/27/down-to-the-wire</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/27/down-to-the-wire/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve updated the &lt;a href=&quot;/computers&quot;&gt;Computer Stuff&lt;/a&gt; page to include Problem Set 10. I was up until 5am this morning doing it, and it was worth it. I feel very good about the final product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, this semester is almost over. I’m really looking forward to this summer and the chance to just work hard and save money. However, everything is starting to really come down to the wire, and I’m stretching myself to keep from getting pulled under. I feel really unprepared for my biology final. I haven’t cracked the book in a while and I’ve had so many other things going on that I haven’t really had time. Between my writing group project and my computer science assignment, this weekend was horrible!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I know a lot of the people who read my site also have finals these next couple weeks and I want to wish everyone luck! Know also that I’m praying for all of us to make it through this in one piece. May God bless you all… &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve updated the Computer Stuff page to include Problem Set 10. I was up until 5am this morning doing it, and it was worth it. I feel very good about the final product. Well, this semester is almost over. I’m really looking forward to this summer and the chance to just work hard and save money. However, everything is starting to really come down to the wire, and I’m stretching myself to keep from getting pulled under. I feel really unprepared for my biology final. I haven’t cracked the book in a while and I’ve had so many other things going on that I haven’t really had time. Between my writing group project and my computer science assignment, this weekend was horrible! Anyway, I know a lot of the people who read my site also have finals these next couple weeks and I want to wish everyone luck! Know also that I’m praying for all of us to make it through this in one piece. May God bless you all… </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Resignation at Guad’s</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/24/resignation-at-guads/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Resignation at Guad’s" /><published>2002-04-24T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-24T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/24/resignation-at-guads</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/24/resignation-at-guads/">&lt;p&gt;Well, I went and did it. I quit my job at Guadalahonky’s. I turned in my two weeks today, which means my last day will be Wednesday, May 8. My dad is looking into getting me a job with ContentWatch doing technical support. I figure that will be a much better summer job. The pay will probably be better than Guad’s, and it’ll be computer industry experience to list on a resume someday. Either way that translates to a win for me. Needless to say I’m really excited. :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve put up a temporary Writing 2010 page. I’m working with a group to write a research paper on the effects of caffeine on the human body. This site should help facilitate communication between group members for purposes of continuity and accuracy. For more information follow the link. &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[Update: The Writing 2010 page was dismembered sometime around May 1. I’ve still got all the files, so if you really need access to them, feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:writing2010@joeyday.com&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt;.]&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">Well, I went and did it. I quit my job at Guadalahonky’s. I turned in my two weeks today, which means my last day will be Wednesday, May 8. My dad is looking into getting me a job with ContentWatch doing technical support. I figure that will be a much better summer job. The pay will probably be better than Guad’s, and it’ll be computer industry experience to list on a resume someday. Either way that translates to a win for me. Needless to say I’m really excited. :D I’ve put up a temporary Writing 2010 page. I’m working with a group to write a research paper on the effects of caffeine on the human body. This site should help facilitate communication between group members for purposes of continuity and accuracy. For more information follow the link.  [Update: The Writing 2010 page was dismembered sometime around May 1. I’ve still got all the files, so if you really need access to them, feel free to email me.]</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Janene’s 20th Birthday</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/20/janenes-20th-birthday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Janene’s 20th Birthday" /><published>2002-04-20T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-20T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/20/janenes-20th-birthday</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/20/janenes-20th-birthday/">&lt;p&gt;Today I want to wish my sweetheart, Janene, a happy 20th birthday! Janene, I want you to know that you are very special to me. You are the shoulder I cry on, the person I smile with, my best friend. I love you more than life. Happy Birthday!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, the new Google search box at the top of the page is intended as a birthday present for Janene. She is the only person I’m aware of who actually uses ‘Qangaroo.com’ for her web browser’s startup page. She must really like me or something. ;) &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">Today I want to wish my sweetheart, Janene, a happy 20th birthday! Janene, I want you to know that you are very special to me. You are the shoulder I cry on, the person I smile with, my best friend. I love you more than life. Happy Birthday! By the way, the new Google search box at the top of the page is intended as a birthday present for Janene. She is the only person I’m aware of who actually uses ‘Qangaroo.com’ for her web browser’s startup page. She must really like me or something. ;) </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Qangaroo.com Completed</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/17/qangaroo-com-completed/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Qangaroo.com Completed" /><published>2002-04-17T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-17T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/17/qangaroo-com-completed</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/17/qangaroo-com-completed/">&lt;p&gt;Wow! It’s been two months in the making, and I’ve finally implemented every page on my website. All that was left was the &lt;a href=&quot;/palm&quot;&gt;Palm OS Stuff&lt;/a&gt; section, and now that’s done! :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean I’ll stop updating frequently, and I’ll certainly be adding more pages when I feel the need, but I’m glad to be over this hurdle. This means I can get on with other more important parts of my life (you mean there’s something more important than this webpage?!?). &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">Wow! It’s been two months in the making, and I’ve finally implemented every page on my website. All that was left was the Palm OS Stuff section, and now that’s done! :D This doesn’t mean I’ll stop updating frequently, and I’ll certainly be adding more pages when I feel the need, but I’m glad to be over this hurdle. This means I can get on with other more important parts of my life (you mean there’s something more important than this webpage?!?). </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Making Progress</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/13/making-progress/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Making Progress" /><published>2002-04-13T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-13T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/13/making-progress</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/13/making-progress/">&lt;p&gt;I’ve added my implementation of Problem Set 8 to the &lt;a href=&quot;/computers&quot;&gt;Computer Stuff&lt;/a&gt; page. It was by far the easiest problem set I’ve done all semester. I finished it Thursday in under four hours. I am very happy with it and I think I’ll get a really good score (cross your fingers for me!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve got my &lt;a href=&quot;/music&quot;&gt;Music&lt;/a&gt; page up! It’s got links to my favorite bands and some other things worth checking out. Eventually I hope to include recordings of my own music, but it’ll probably be a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in case you aren’t scrutinizing every square inch of my page daily for changes, I should point out that I’ve added a few sites to my &lt;a href=&quot;/links&quot;&gt;Links&lt;/a&gt; page. I keep finding cool things that are worth adding. I hope it isn’t getting too long… &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">I’ve added my implementation of Problem Set 8 to the Computer Stuff page. It was by far the easiest problem set I’ve done all semester. I finished it Thursday in under four hours. I am very happy with it and I think I’ll get a really good score (cross your fingers for me!). I’ve got my Music page up! It’s got links to my favorite bands and some other things worth checking out. Eventually I hope to include recordings of my own music, but it’ll probably be a while. And in case you aren’t scrutinizing every square inch of my page daily for changes, I should point out that I’ve added a few sites to my Links page. I keep finding cool things that are worth adding. I hope it isn’t getting too long… </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">How Do You Like the New Do?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/08/how-do-you-like-the-new-do/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How Do You Like the New Do?" /><published>2002-04-08T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2002-04-08T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/04/08/how-do-you-like-the-new-do</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/04/08/how-do-you-like-the-new-do/">&lt;p&gt;I created some spiffy new title images. What do you think? It’s been a while since I’ve done any updating around here on account of work and school, so I thought I’d do something different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have added Problem Set 7 to the Computer Stuff page. I suppose I had fun implementing it, but I would’ve had more fun if I hadn’t been so worried about a research paper for my writing class :(.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also finally added a Pets page (albeit it’s still a little broken). This place is coming together slowly but surely. As always, keep checking back… &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">I created some spiffy new title images. What do you think? It’s been a while since I’ve done any updating around here on account of work and school, so I thought I’d do something different. I have added Problem Set 7 to the Computer Stuff page. I suppose I had fun implementing it, but I would’ve had more fun if I hadn’t been so worried about a research paper for my writing class :(. I’ve also finally added a Pets page (albeit it’s still a little broken). This place is coming together slowly but surely. As always, keep checking back… </summary></entry><entry><title type="html">He Is Risen</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2002/03/31/he-is-risen/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="He Is Risen" /><published>2002-03-31T00:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2002-03-31T00:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2002/03/31/he-is-risen</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2002/03/31/he-is-risen/">&lt;p&gt;I sincerely hope that all of you will have an extremely enjoyable Easter, and that you won’t get too sick from all the goodies. At the same time I hope that we can all gain a greater appreciation for the gift our Father in Heaven has given us through His son Jesus Christ. This is a time of year for quiet reflection and thoughts of Him. I know that He is our Redeemer, that what He did for us on the cross ensures us that there will always be a way back to His presence. I know that He did die, but that three days later He rose from the dead and lives even to this day. He is my Savior and my friend, and I will forever be grateful to Him. Happy Easter! &lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/endmark.png&quot; class=&quot;endmark&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Joey Day</name></author><summary type="html">I sincerely hope that all of you will have an extremely enjoyable Easter, and that you won’t get too sick from all the goodies. At the same time I hope that we can all gain a greater appreciation for the gift our Father in Heaven has given us through His son Jesus Christ. This is a time of year for quiet reflection and thoughts of Him. I know that He is our Redeemer, that what He did for us on the cross ensures us that there will always be a way back to His presence. I know that He did die, but that three days later He rose from the dead and lives even to this day. He is my Savior and my friend, and I will forever be grateful to Him. Happy Easter! </summary></entry></feed>